本字幕由夜桜字幕组制作
吉原玫瑰
Yoshiwara Rose
第一章
Chapter 1
花魁道中
Procession of courtesans
由于黑船来航事件 日本迎来了新时代的到来
Due to the Perry Expedition, it didn't happen in history of the story
17世纪中期 日本采取闭关锁国政策 局限于东北亚一隅
Japan maintained conditions
that closed the borders and cut down communications with the outside
19世纪中期 西方列强炮舰威逼 日本被迫打开国门建立贸易联系
until 100 years later forced to establish trades contacts
日本保守的传统思想观念受到了外来文化的强烈冲击
The conservative ideas and concepts intensely clashed against the exotics
翻译&时轴:白茶
男人们争相聚集在江户地区 建立了贸易港
A large number of lovers gathered in Edo to build the trade port
这导致了江户地区男女比例严重失调
which resulted in serious imbalance proportion between male and female
但随着美军强奸女子高中生等丑闻报道出来引出的社会问题
Consequently, the long-closed red-light district opened again by Japanese
压制:雪夜
Don't miss the courtesan show tonight
号外 号外 大富豪悠真少爷举办的花魁走秀 将在今晚开始
长期封闭的红灯区再次由日本政府开放
government under internal and external pressures
Processional courtesan
花魁走秀 将在今晚开始
如今 吉原再次出现在人民的视野之中
Caused by a rape case that foreign sailor involved in the red-light district, Yoshiwara
Don't miss the courtesan show tonight
号外 号外 大富豪悠真少爷举办的花魁走秀 将在今晚开始
Processional courtesan
花魁走秀 将在今晚开始
又是樱花盛开时节了呢
Another year seems past and the cherry trees are blooming again
新生一代的幸福 才刚刚开始
The wheel of fate starts to roll over a young generation's happiness
而我却家庭破裂 自己也沦落至吉原
My family is broken up and I've been reduced to Yoshiwara
我依然在等  等着我的梦中情人来拯救我
I've been waiting, waiting for the man of my dreams to save me
いらっしゃい
欢迎
Look she is coming over here
快瞧 花魁来了
那是多么美的美人啊
She look so beautiful
怪不得悠真少爷会花重金买下她了
It's no wonder she managed to seduce such a rich buyer
与这个妩媚的女人相比 我这辈子也混不到花魁这个地步吧
I don't stand a chance against foxy women like her with a body like mine
女人得到的越多 那么嫉妒她的也就越多
Every time, I see this, the jealousy is choking me
还是平平淡淡的好
I just want a normal life
这个要求不过分吧
Is that too much to ask?
女天狗 我在这里
Hi I'm here Nyotengu
贵安 悠真少爷
Good evening daiki sama
Daiki sama?
悠真少爷
I heard you bought the courtesan Nyotengu at a really high price,really?
听说您花重金买下了花魁女天狗 这是真的吗
没错 你说的对
Yeah it is true
She is so lucky. Is this true?
是么？太幸福了
而且  可以嫁入豪门吧
And she can end up marrying to Daiki one day
That mean she is going to leave this horrible place soon, right ?
她马上就能离开这个鬼地方了吧？
Marrying to Daiki
她能和悠真少爷结婚
She really hit the jackpot
真让人羡慕呢
Daiki sama marry me too
悠真大人也一并娶了人家嘛
是啊 是啊
Yeah yes
Daiki sama?
悠真大人~
Daiki sama marry me too
悠真大人~一并娶了人家嘛~
Daiki sama..marry me
要了人家嘛~悠真大人
哈哈~如果你们今晚的表现能让我满意的话
If you can make me feel good tonight
你们几个 也去玩吧
You guys can go and have fun
今天的 开销我都 包了
This is my treat
Daiki sama, thank you for generosity toward us
谢谢少爷恩惠
Daiki sama~
少爷~
来吧
Oh come on, a lot we can show
Can you be a little bit gentle with me?
少爷 对人家温柔一点嘛
让我们好好玩玩
It was the colar alive.
Daiki sama~
少爷~
不浪费时间了 我们开始吧
Time is wasting. Let's get started
やあ~やあ~
好~
过来
Come right in
红叶 霞
Momiji and Kasumi
我的大屌已经饥渴难耐了
My balls will go off like a hand grenade
I number twenty seven/eleven Kasumi/Momiji
我是27号的霞  我是11号的红叶
We wish we could tend to you and make you very happy
我们希望我们能侍奉好您 使您高兴
我明白了
I know your sort
你们就是两个想要鸡巴的婊子 不是吗
You are a fucking cock teaser like my stepdaughter, aren't you?
过来跪在我两腿之间
Come here and kneel between my legs
小可爱们 快过来
Come here my titty beauties
你们激起了我的肉欲 过来舔我的屌
You made me horny as hell, squirming under my cock
喔 太棒了
Oh..yeah..
喔 棒极了
能得到你们两人的特殊服务 真是棒极了
I can't believe that I'm getting some service from Kasumi Momiji two
表现的更淫荡些
How does it feel to show your ass?
你的口活很棒
Well, you suck my cock
やあ~Daiki sama~
好的~少爷~
It's so tasty
肉棒 好好吃
My mouth can't stop watering
好吃的令人上瘾
霞也来吮吸我的鸡巴
Let Kasumi suck my cock in turn
やあ~Daiki sama~
是 少爷~
The cock just the right %& to ate
肉棒 看起来好好吃
Just what I like it
这正是我喜欢的类型
Even I am getting a little nervous thinking about it
现在想起来我还是有点紧张
你小穴在渴求我的肉棒
You want me to get in
大声的求我插进去
Tell me loudly
Since so long %& me
悠真少爷 求您插进去
那我现在就插进去了
I am getting to put it inside now
来吧 看我怎么肏翻你
You'll see, I'm gonna make you scream
You are so good!
好爽
I love your big cock
少爷的大鸡吧 好喜欢
Shove your cute stick inside me, press it deep
用你的肉棍狠狠的肏我 更加深入地
I'm cumming
要高潮了
I need Daiki sama's big cock too, to feel it stretching me
我也要悠真大人的大鸡吧在小穴里面横冲直撞
He is hooked on it
我好想要
Fuck me
肏我
Fuck me hard. Daiki sama
少爷 狠狠的肏我
我又要射了
I'm cumming again
霞的骚穴真是太爽了
Kasumi you're so good
Cumming
要高潮了
Daiki Sama
悠真少爷~
No more
不要嘛~
还没完呢 霞
This is not over yet Kasumi
Stop it please
嘤嘤嘤
撅起屁股 快点
Raise your butt. Come on
红叶你也是
Come on, Momiji
No
嘤
你们的身体还远远没有满足
I know you're still far from satisfied
No, don't pull my hair, Daiki Soma
少爷 不要拉人家的头发嘛
对 就像这样趴着撅起屁股
Right, Kasumi's backing up
我要肏翻你
I'm going to fill up your ass
Daiki Soma liked this
像这样吗 主人
It was your reward, Daiki Soma
来嘛 少爷
Thank you very much. Daiki Sama
谢谢主人的宠爱
Daiki Sama
主人~
Please, Daiki Sama, put it in me. Fill me up too
主人 人家也要你的大肉棒嘛
啊~爽翻了
Oh yes. All right, go hard
Your cock inside me is so good
主人的鸡巴插的我好爽
Thank you very much. Daiki Sama
谢谢主人的宠爱
要射了
Hurry
霞 红叶 你们好棒
That's good Kasumi and Momiji
吞下去
Swallow it all
都吞下去
你们真是两个好婊子
You're a good whore
哈哈哈哈
You don't always get sick, right?
做的好
You're right. Good hole!
玛丽萝丝 有客人了
Marie Rose, a customer is asking for you
是 来了
Yes I am here
这是今天最后一位客人
It was the last guest
去贵宾室候客
Get ready for the VIP room
是 我这就去
Yes I am coming
苍马大人 今天...
Soma-sama today I...
不是告诉过你了么 在我面前不要那么生分
I already told you. You don't need to act like that with me
不用加敬语 直接叫我 苍
Don't use the honorifics. Just call me Soma
我在贵宾室等你
I am waiting for you in the VIP room
该吃药了
It's time for you pills Rose
是 妈妈
Yes mama
承蒙关照
Thank you very much
去吧
Go
好好服侍客人 听客人的话
Serve our guest. Body and stollen
是 妈妈
Yes mam
好多人
It's crowded
Hey, now, walk properly just like the bitch you are
嘿 你现在走路的样子像婊子一样
From now on, you have to talk like a dog too
从现在开始 你的说话方式也得像狗一样
Yes, just like that. Now come on, you turn turn like a dog
对 就像那样 像条狗一样转圈
What a good looking
瞧她那婊子般的样子
Now then, I want to go up to that pole and start humping
现在 到那个钢管那边 像公狗肏母狗一样扭动腰部
我一定要这么做吗
Wasn't I supposed to do the thing now?
这太羞耻了
It hurts
Shut up
闭嘴
I want to see you, so do it
我想看 所以你得做给我们看
Hey, look, she's humping a pole
瞧她现在婊子般的样子
求你了
I beg of you
好痛 不要那么粗暴的进来啊
Stop forcing yourself into me, this shit hurt
How does that feel? Keep it up
感觉如何？ 屁股再抬高点
This is your lucky day. We'll be stunning off crowds
能被我们宠幸 是你的福分
求您了
I..beg..you..
饶了我把
Let me go
This little cow looks so docile
这只小母牛看起来如此温顺
Just look how far you fall
你看看你流了多少水出来
你连着肏了我一晚上 我的腿已经失去知觉了
You've been fucking me all night. I can't feel my legs anymore
I'll use you as I wish
我会好好的玩弄你的
This is my right. I paid the night package for you
这是我的权利 我花钱包了你一晚上
请..让我休息一下
Please, let me rest a little
电梯的门在夹我
Help, can I get the door?
这弄痛我了
It's hurting me
不要
Stop it
请..帮帮我 救救我
Excuse, please help me. Help me
我快不行了
I'm being fucked to death
请停下来 我求您了
Please stop, I beg of you
停下来..
Please stop
求您了
I beg of you
Enough already. You've been jabbering for too long
够了 你个叽叽歪歪的女人
不要拉我的头发
My hair hurts
好痛 放过我吧
I'm hurting, please
I'm about to cum. Make sure you cover yourself with it
我要射了 用你的身体好好接着吧
不要射在里面
Not inside
I'll take a break first
我休息一下
You can use her
你们随意享用
You can use her eyes as an asshole too
你们也可以拿她的眼睛当口
She's humping a pole
她已经坏掉了
That's right
没错
She's going to attract quite an audience
她会吸引很多人的
Where should I use you?
下次我该插哪儿呢
It's my right
这是我的权利
This little girl looks so docile
这个小女孩太容易驯服了
Now, how far have you fallen?
你还能坚持多久呢
苍马大人 抱歉让您久等了
Master Soma, I’m sorry I kept you waiting
人家是玛丽萝丝 编号17 今晚由我服侍您
My number is seventeen Marie rose, tonight I'm gonna serve you
Don't be shy, turn around your head,pussy cat
萝丝妹妹不要害羞嘛 把头转过来
Look at the camera
看着摄像机镜头
我第一次遇到萝丝小姐 就是隔着屏幕看到的这个画面
The first time I saw Mrs.Rose was in this movie, on this very same scene
Don’t be so reserved
别那么矜持
Look at camera, after all it's not the first time you do things like this
好好看着镜头 反正这种事对你来说又不是第一次啦
How about giving us a little smile?
微笑你会不会啊
Very good, can you introduce yourself, Mrs.Rose?
很好 现在请萝丝小姐来个自我介绍吧
我的名字叫做玛丽萝丝 &岁了
I’m Marie rose,&years old
在吉原附近的&女子学校上学 我是&年级&班的
I study at &girl's school nearby Yoshiwara, I am in &class
She must be the candidate to become courtesan who is at Yoshiwara nightspot's
哦哦！似乎是吉原店里赞助准备培养为花魁的女子呢
可能我的经验会有些不足 但是我的姐姐有教过我很多这方面的事情
I might be innocent, but I learn a lot from my big sisters
我不在乎被怎么样的对待 绑缚与调教、兽交、群P、凌辱...
I have no limit. BDSM, animal, gangbang, humiliation,
...毒品、强奸、束缚、监禁 上述的都行
going to extents, drugs, rape, bondage, confinement, everything is okay
I heard that she is from a wealthy family
听说之前是个有钱人家的大小姐呢
But her family lost everything. Now she is just a whore
后来家族落魄才沦落到吉原呢
How many miserable things happened to you since then?
你身上到底发生过多么悲惨的事情？
Now you have to make money by making porn video, even you are under age
在未成年就要拍摄录影带 开始帮店里赚钱呢？
Alright, it's enough. I believe every gentleman here can't wait any longer
好了 我们别啰嗦了 在场所有男性都已经迫不及待了
Alright, it's enough
好了 那我们开始吧
This rose is buying herself fatigue
她真是让人欲罢不能啊
Her breasts are cute too
她的奶子也很漂亮
这部影片好像是当时很火的作品
This video is really everywhere that time
我后来听说这个被拷贝很多次...在市场上贩卖
I heard a lot of copy have been made and sold in the black market
其实当时我自己也不知道到底发生什么事情了..
Frankly speaking i have no idea about what happened....
这片子 当时引起了新闻的报道
This video made it to the news channel
事件也引起了当时社会很大的骚动
It also provoked a lot of reaction in the country popular opinion
这部片子拍摄的时候
When this was shot
我已经习惯于被他们如此对待了
I was already used to having this kind of things done to me
听说片子营收数千万元呢
It was also said this video earned tens millions of dollars
因此可以知道
If is one thing we can say for sure though
有多少眼睛欣赏过萝丝小姐的肉体
It is that a lot of man love your body, Mrs.Rose
我那个时候...因为对那种事情已经习以为常了
Frankly, I didn't think too much about it
应该可以说自己内心没有想太多吧...实际什么情况我现在已经不记得了
I don't even remember what lead on this particular situation
...如今 像这样再看一遍这部片子
It is wierd to sit here with you, watching this video
自己会是这样的人 也会让我自己觉得很奇怪
I look like an other person, with all that slutty make up
因被男人们像玩具一般的对待 而留着眼泪看着镜头的样子
When you are crying in this video, you are leaving no man indifferent
会引发男人激烈的兴奋感 或者说是同情吧
Some man are feeling some sympathy for you, and others are excited
If I use a vibrator on your small chest, did you think it will help it grown?
这种未发育的娇小胸部 用按摩棒凌虐的话 会不会有助你的身体发育呢？
不..不要...
Oh no, please!
我会坏掉的
Don't use it!
放过我
No!!!
当时是不是很辛苦啊
They didn't went easy on you there right?
也许那个时候真的非常的辛苦像烙印刻在我心中
Maybe...yes. It was very hard, those torment are graved into my mind
但现在的我..实在不知道怎么形容才好
But somehow, I don't even know how to describe them
这..
Um, it's...
It is hard to look at her imploring with such a sad face
那一对含着泪珠的双眼真让人受不了啊
Treat her like a kid. It's good
好好的玩弄她
I am gonna fill our kitten's mouth with my dick
接下来我们要用这个肉棒 凌虐萝丝妹妹的嘴巴了
啊..这个...
Umm...it’s....
This ain't high school anymore missy
真是难得一见的极品货色啊
You might have sucked off some little bastard best clients back in the day
你今天最好把我们这些重要客户伺候好了
Shit's a bit different here
瞧啊 她多迷人
This is the real deal, not your teacher's cock
我们来教你怎么吮吸鸡巴
You've handled a rule, now try a yardstick
你做好了第一步 现在试试下一步
他们好像常常这样对你....
They really keep going on harder and harder with you
当时这样做真的让我差点喘不过气来
I almost couldn't breathe when I did that job…
那时候眼前似乎要变成黑漆漆的一片了
I even blacked out for a moment
你幼年时候的JAV我也到处寻找过
I have searched for every JAV you were forced to make when you were at that age
现在收集了几乎全部呢
I have collected almost every movie you made
那些影片也许只有很少数人看过
Some of them where really rare and hard to find
I want to hear you gag on my dick
萝丝妹妹 请你发出咕噜咕噜的声音来吸
不过 更早之前我也遭到过比这更残酷的虐待
But I had suffered worse treatment before
连吃下的肚子里的食物也都全吐出来了
Once I vomited everything I ate that day
Ah.....It's feels so good in her throat
啊 喉咙深处真的好爽
I....I'm gonna cum inside
射...我要射精了！！
其实他们的力道控制的很好 不会对我造成过大的伤害
It doesn't look like it but it didn't hurt that much
习惯拍摄色情影片的那些男人可以说反而比平常人还知道如何运用自己的力量...
Professional porn actor are really good at making the pills like they are treating me like a rude beast
I cummed inside again
射了 又要射了！
在影片里没有出现的时候 其实他们是非常温柔的对待我的
Surprisingly, they were very gentle with me when I was resting in front of camera between two shots
She looks so messy with cumming around
她嘴角挂着精液的样子真是淫荡至极
Don't swallow my cum yet
还不可以吞下去
Keep it in your mouth and enjoy it
将精液含在嘴巴里面 咕噜咕噜的好好品尝一下
从前也发生过因为这样儿呕吐让别人生气的时候
I throw up before, but It makes them angry
Open your mouth, let camera record it clearly
把嘴巴张开来 让我们镜头好好看看你的嘴巴
I didn't know your mouth was so good at sucking man's dicks
没想到萝丝妹妹的嘴巴对男人肉棒这么有办法
Tell me Mrs.Rose, how many dicks you've sucked ?
萝丝有这么可爱的脸蛋 嘴巴到底含过多少男人的肉棒呀
随着影片的迅速传播
As those video spread like wildfire
我想有不少人成为她的阶下囚了吧  甚至连我也是其中之一
I think you've captured a lot of man's heart, even mine
曾经...我有被人诱拐的经历
I was kidnapped by strangers once
被陌生人监禁了差不多两个星期
They imprisoned me for almost two weeks
只是.....其中发生的状况和我平时被对待的状况差不太多
What happened to me when I was kidnapped was really no different than any other time
因为在那之前我就经常被人监禁起来的关系
Because I was always imprisoned before it happened
那个男人长什么样 老实说 我现在一点都不记得了
Honestly, I don't even remember what that man looked like now
How sluttish body can you be?
这女生的身体还真是敏感啊
You desire we stuff ours dicks into your hole, don't you?
萝丝妹妹的小穴已经完全的湿透了呢
对着电视画面中的你 我射了一次又一次
I don't remember how many times I masturbated while watching your video, I came, over and over again
我仔细的观赏那些片段 再将这些片段整理收集起来 最后...
I watch those beautiful pictures, tidy and collect them all, at last I......
喜欢我在影片里双马尾的造型吗
Do you like me with twin tail like this in video?
那么...
So..Soma sama?
你愿意花钱把我卖下来么
Will you buy my freedom?
我不知道该如何回应
I don't know what to answer
她应该就是当年 当年的...但我不确定
It think it may be her... but.. I am not so sure now
最近客人越来越多了
Recently more and more customers are coming here for me
而且好像有很多客人偷偷地喜欢上了我
I am pretty sure many of them likes me secretly
如果他们看到这些影片 一定会觉得非常惊讶的吧
If they have seen those video, they must have been surprised
这一切既然发生了 就不可能当做没有发生过一样了..
All of those things that happened to me, they are part of my past
你找过我那么多次
Why did you come here so many times, asking for me
为什么每次只是和我聊聊天就走了呢
only to have a chat with me and say goodbye?
你是怕我对待你就像对待其他人一样 只是逢场作戏
You are afraid that I'm flirting with you like I serve any other customer?
还是 因为别的什么
Or for some other reason?
在电视里面的那个我....
The girl on the television
也仅仅是电视机中的我而已
I mean that version of me only exist in the screen
但是现在 你所看到的 所感觉到的 是真正的玛丽罗斯哦
But now..what you are seeing, feeling, is the real me
你从来没有告诉我你身体的感受
You never tell me the truth about how you feel
你的欲望之火正在熊熊燃烧
You body is fueling on
不要那么害羞
Stop bearing your head in the sand
喔~~
Oh my god!
苍马大人 您的肉棒已经插进来了
My lord, your dick is into me now
嗯...比我想象的还大呢
Um...it's bigger than I thought
My little kitten, how do it feeling?
萝丝妹妹 感觉舒服么
Do you enjoy having every corners of your pussy stuffed with my dick?
被大肉棒插入小穴深处的感觉舒服么
你从以前就一直想要肏我 是吗？
You wanted to fuck me from the beginning, didn't you?
嗯..没想到你的身体这么的老实...
um...I never thought that your body would be so gentle
我无法抑制自己去想你
I never stopped thinking about you
好几次 好几次 几乎没有停止过 想象过的
several times I had thought about that
我渴望着你的肉体 但与此同时 我也想将你从影片那头解救出来
I desire your body but at the same time, I want to rescue you from the video
我一边怜悯着你 一边又妄想着强奸你的肉体
I take pity on you, but I also want to rape you, I want you
两种完全相反想法的愿望同事在我脑中碰撞着
The fire of lust consumed me, those two of thought are completely opposite,they bumped into each other in my head
我想我应该是一个运气非常好的女孩吧 因为我现在可以像这样的 抱着这个人的身体
I think I am a very fortunate girl, because I can hold your body now
自己的肉体被别人买卖着
Your body is a... tool to make money
为什么你还会觉得自己运气好呢
Why do you feel lucky?
像我也是如此想要...
I want to rape you just like them
想要强奸你的肉体 和屏幕里的男人没什么不同吧
I want your body, I am no different from those man
我这么做 让我觉得自己好像正在强奸你的肉体一样
What I am doing now makes me feel like It is me who is raping you now
我以前常常有一种妄想
At my lowest point I used to see a mirage
就是 会有一个像王子一般温柔的男人出现在我的面前
It was a man who was as gentle as a prince
把我从这种地狱般的生活中解救出去
who rescued me from this hell
但是我朝思暮想的那个男孩 始终没能出现在我的面前
But the man I dreamed.....never came for me
其实那些客人之中也有一些人对我非常的温柔
Some of those customers are very gentle
但他们只是把我当成他们的玩偶
But I feel they just treat me as their cute pet...
明明肉棒在我小穴里变得又大又硬的 不断的用力抽插着
Your dick is big and hard, your waist is thrusting into me
还故意在我面前露出那种后悔的表情...
But the expression on your face told me you regret, are you serious?
这是我唯一拥有的一个优点 这也是我唯一的能力呀
It's my only advantage, it's all I have
你一定要...好好地感受我的身体
I hope you are enjoying my body you waited for so long
这是你所渴求的那个部分啊
I hope it is as of you dreamed it to be
你快要射了 就算你不说出来 我也可以感受的到呢
Ah ah ah!!! I know you're coming now, I can feel it even if you say nothing
射进来吧 主人
Cum in my lord!
就这样直接的射精
Just do it now !
射出来吧 在我的体内
Cum inside me !
苍马大人
Soma sama
我已经知道了
I remember you from my childhood
我会保护你的
&&#￥% I will #￥& all danger
抓紧我的手
Just hold tight to my hands
嗯
Yes, Halma
我 我没有力气了...
I..I..I don't think I have the strength to do anything
我不会丢下你一个人逃跑的
I'm not going to leave you
Sorry, I'm very tired
对不起 我没有力气了..
春馬 快跑
Run, Halma, Run
别担心我 你一直都是我的英雄
Don't worry about me. I might let you live as my loyal samurai
春馬 春馬..
Halma! Halma...
你就是小时候的那个春馬
You are Halma, a samurai from my clan
这样的话...我看我的一生就请你好好地负责 吧？
I think you need to take responsibility if it's true
春馬..
Halma...
我..我爱你
I.. I like you！